Guide to the 2000 Voting Technology Archive.
Voting Technology Archive, 2000
- Series II: E-voting and the 2004 Election
  - Perfect Voting System, December 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Letter About Paper Trail (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Letter to Technical Guidelines Development Committee, April 17, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - US Cities Rocked by 'Computer Ate My Vote' Protest, April 17, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Count Crisis?, May 13, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Cyber-Voting, Version 1.0, January 28, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Declaration of Henry E. Brady, August 3 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Democrats Push for Paper, April 16, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Did God Tell Them to Steal The Votes (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Checks and Balances in Elections Equipment and Procedures, July 30, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Diebold Knew of Legal Risks, April 20, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Toward the Secure and Practical E-Elections in New Era (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - E-Voting Machines Run Into Some Problems, March 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Towards Secure and Practical E-Elections in the New Era (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - E-Voting Machines Run Into Some Problems, March 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - E-Voting or Punch Cards, October 27, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Testimony, May 5, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - What Really happened in Venezuela, September 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Effects from 2000 Election Still Seen, February 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Ohio's Disabled Voters: Ignored Again, January 18, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Election Scandals, Past and Future, December 4, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Letter to Representative John Conyers Jr., April 15, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Is Electronic Vote Compatible with Democracy (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Our Beef with E-Voting, January 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Evaluation of Edison/Mitofsky Election System 2004, January 19, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Federal Appeals Court Dismisses Electronic Voting Machine Lawsuit, October 29, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Fla. Voting Machines Pass Primary Test, September 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Florida Shuns Paper Backup of Computer Ballots, February 19, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Mistakes in Voting Plunge, State Report Says, February 2, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Global Lessons in E-Voting: States Can Learn From Success, Fraud Abroad, September 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Hack the Vote, December 2, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - The 2004 Florida Optical Voting Machine Controversy, November 14, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Those Interested in Punch Card Performance, October 17, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Histpry of Voting System Standards Program, November 1998 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - How Did Ohio's Voting Equipment Fare in 2004, February 8, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - No Confidence Vote: Why the Current Touchscreen Fiasco (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - In Touch Screens We Trust, February 9, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Will Your November Vote Count, April 23, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - ITAA Calls Electronic Voting A Major Success, November 3, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - ITAA Response to Anti E-Voting Campaign, July 14, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Electronic Voting Machine and Voting Cards Activate Machines (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Composition of Electronic Voting System (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Latest Development and Current Situation: An Assessment, October 24, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - First Hanging Chad Case Heads to Trial, July 26, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Section 5.3- Recounts and Other Remedies, October 20, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Mock the Vote, October 29, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Mostly Good Reviews for Electronic Voting, November 12, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Chad 2.0, November 2003 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Diebold's Political Machine, March 5, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Electronic Voting Results Questioned, April 24, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - New Reports Cast Doubt on Internet Voting, February 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Ninth Circuit Reject Constitutional Challenge to Touchscreen Voting, October 29, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Technical Guidelines Development Committee, April 20, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - An Assessment of Voting Technology and Ballot Design, December 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Usability Testing in the Development Cycle, December 11, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Closing Remarks, Decmber 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Confidence-- What it is and How You Can Achieve It, December 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Conformation Testing: An Industry Perspective, December 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Consensus Issues, December 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Do Paper Trails Help?, December 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Electronic Voting and Security (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Georgia Voting System Security Features (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Glossary of U.S. Voting Systems (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Improving Usability and Accessability of Voting Systems, May 2004 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Openess and Security (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - NIST's Role in Standard and Testing, December 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Is It Plugged In?, December 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Security Issues in Voting Systems: A Panel Session, December 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Software Issues in Voting Systems, December 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Starting from People (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Usability and Accessability Panel (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Voter Verified Paper Ballot De Facto Discrimination (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - No Doctored DRE, July 27, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Effective Use of Computing Technology in Vote Tallying, March 1975 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Printouts of 2004 Ohio County Votes (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Directive 2005-07, April 14, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Ohio Recount Procedure (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Ohio's Disabled Voters: Ignored Again, January 19, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Electronic Voting Machine, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - NIST Ignores Scientific Method for Voting Technology, December 16, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Paper Receipts No Guarantee, February 23, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Paper v. Electronic Voting Records An Assessment, April 2004 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Pleading and Discovery in an Ohio Election Contest, December 7, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Voting- Machine Woes in Carteret Have Officials Looking for Answers, November 23, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Problems With Provisional Ballots, November 11, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Paper or Touchscreen (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Provisional Ballot Procedure by State, October 29, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Provisional Ballot Update, January 25, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Provisional Ballot Update, February 8, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Provisional Ballot Update, December 7, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Provisional Voting, October 15, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Punch Card System Sees Its Last Election, October 7, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Risk Assessment Report, September 2, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - San Francisco: New Voting Method, November 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Voting Machines and the Underestimate of the Bush Vote, November 12, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Inside A U.S. Election Vote Counting Program, July 8, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Sludge Report #154- Bigger Than Watergate, July 8, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - U.S. Election Integrity Flaw Discovered At Diebold, February 10, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Opinion and Analysis: Voting and Disability (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Statutes for States Provisional Ballot Deadlines, October 25, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Separating Myths from Reality (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - NASS Side-by-Side Analysis of Federal Legislation on Voter, December 19, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Touchscreen Voting Nixed Here, May 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - State Bans Electronic Balloting in 4, May 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - State Recounts Laws, September 12, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - State Report on Provisional Voting, Novmebr 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Supplemental Declaration of Henry E. Brady, October 7, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - State by State Provisional Ballot Guidelines, October 18, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Trusted Agent Report Diebold Accuvote- TS Voting System, January 20, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Technicians, Lawmakers, try to do Away with Chads, March 23, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Grad Student Center of Diebold Controversy, November 12, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SGA Results Voided; New Election Coming Next Month, March 20, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Disenfranchisement of Voters Under Legal Guardianship, November 11, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The History of Voting Machines (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Voting 1.0 and No Time to Upgrade, November 28, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - On New Fraud Voting Machine, The Same Old Fraud, April 27, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Florida's Bad Record on Voting Records, July 29, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - On the Voting Machine Maker's Tab, September 12, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Has the Time Come for Touch Screen Voting?, July 28, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Paper Trail Debate, July 27, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Paperless Chase: Electronic Voting and Democratic Values, September 4 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Throwing Votes A Curve Ball, August 25, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Touchscreens reduce Spoiled Ballots, November 22, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Touchscreens Worry Voters, November 10, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - A Study of Voting Technology and Ballot Design (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - White Paper: US Public Opinion Towards Voting Technologies, March 1, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Is the NIST Technical Guidelines Development Committee Working for You, the Voter? (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Users Auction Vote on E-Bay, July 13, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Vote Here Submits Software for Public Scrutiny, September 15, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Vote Count at Mercy of Clandestine Testing, August 23, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Voting Glitches Found in Six Recent Elections, March 31, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Voting Machines: Vote Tampering in the 21st Century, December 2, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - IEEE Voting System Standard, December 10, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Voting Technolotgy for People With Disabilities, March 3 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Voting Technology: From 2000 to 2004... And Beyond (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - State of Maryland Diebold AccuVote- TS Voting System Security Action Plan, September 23, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Wanted: A Legible Voting Ballot: Why it's time to redesign the ballot design, October 6, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Election Panel Tells States Money will Be Coming $2.3 Billion to be Disbursed for Voting Upgades, February 17, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Fairfax Judge Orders Logs of Voting Machines Inspected, November 6, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Fairfax to Probe Voting Machines, November 18, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Florida Again Faces Disputes Over Election Recounts, July 29, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - In ATM's, Not Votes, We Trust, Nvember 17, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - MD Democrats Want Outside Voting Machine Audit, October 21, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - New Voting System Assailed, March 28, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Voting Machine Glitches Prompt GOP Challenge, Novmber 4, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Voting Machine Makers to Fight Security Criticism, December 9, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - What Happens in Ohio, January 10, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Aussies do it Right: E-Voting, November 3, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - California County Keeps E-Vote, September 29, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Challengers Want Ohio Review, December 13, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Computer Loses 4,500 Votes, November 4, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Database Flawed: Not Malevolent, November 23, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Diebold Backs Off Legal Challenge, December 2, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Diebold to Settle E-Voting Suit, November 10, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Dust-Up Over E-Vote Paper Trail, November 26, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - E-Vote Inflates Bush Total, November 5, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - E-Vote Machines Face Audit, August 12, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - E-Vote Snafu in California County, March 19, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - E-Vote Vendors Hand Over Software, October 26, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - E-Voting Tests Get Failing Grade, November 1, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - House Dems Seek Election Inquiry, November 5, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Maryland E-Voting Passes Muster, September 25, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - More Questions for Florida, December 13, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - More Questions for Florida, August 27, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Ohio Recount Stirs Trouble, December 20, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Report: Fewer 2004 Votes Missed, February 14, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Reports of Muddled E-Voting, November 2, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - So Far, Recount Shows No Problem, Novmebr 19, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Students Fight E-Vote Firm, October 21, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Time to Recall E-Vote Machines?, October 6, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Vote Recount to Settle Doubts?, November 17, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Making Democratic Institutions, July 22, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Legal, Operational and Technical Standards for E-Voting, September 30, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - To Assure Prise and Confidence in the Electoral Process, August 1 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - The Unpolitical Animal, August 30, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Permanent Fatal Errors, December 6, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Poll Position, September 20, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - The Onion's Countdown to the Recount, October 27, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Vanishing Votes, May 17, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Get the Vote Out, October 7, 2004 - January 21, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Series III: Voting Technology Reference Material
  - Effective Use of Computing Technology in Vote-Tallying, April 1978 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Accuracy, Integrity, and Security in Computerized Vote- Tallying, August 1988 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Douglas Election Equipment Brochure, August 2000 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Interview with Mark Seibel of teh Miami Herald, December 19, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Hart Intercivic, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Automation and the Electronic Administrator (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - 2001 IFES Buyer's Guide To Election Supplies (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Voting: What is What Could Be, July 2001 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Election Systems and Software (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Interview With Roy E. Saltman, Feb. 19, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Interview with Roy E. Saltman, April 1, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Interview with George Bennett and Joel Engel Hardt of the Palm Beach Post, December 19, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Quality that Gives You the Competitive Edge, June 4, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Certified Voting Systems Used in Florida, December 20, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - The Path to Florida, October 2004 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Voting Machines Must Provide a Voter-Verifiable Audit Trail, March 9, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Fixing the Vote, Octover 2004 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Broken Machine Politics, January 2004 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - To Register Doubts, Press Here, May 15, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - File Sharing Pits Copyright Against Free Speech, November 3, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - The Ballot Reform Imperative, December 17, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Armed to Send Chads into Voting Oblivion, December 17, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - In recount, Confusion is Winner, November 12, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Last Year's Voting Confusion Spurs New Research Interest, November 11, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - An E-Public Sphere for the Digital Age, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - After Florida: The call for Election Reform, March/April 2001 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Elections in Cyberspace: Toward a New Era in American Politics (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - The Machinery of Representation: Voting Technologies and the 2000 Presidential Election, March 16-17, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Trouble in Paradise, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Reports Say Internet Voting is too Insecure to Use, January 21, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - The GIGO Principle and Voting Machines, April 2004 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Electronic Voting: Important Research Questions (Box 12, Folder 104)
- Series IV: Roy G. Saltman Papers on Election Policy and Technology
  - Letter to Mr. Saltman (from Stephen Hilgartner), June 3, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Papers on Election Policy and Techniques Table of Contents, April 1, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Accuracy and Integrity of Computerized Vote-Counting, June 26, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Accuracy, Integrity, and Security in Computerized Vote-Tallying, August 1988 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - The Impact of Computer Technology on Election Administration, April 3, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Effective Use of Computing Technology in Vote Tallying, March 1975 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Letter to Ms. Bonsall, July 31, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Vote-by-Phone-- Promises and Pitfalls, October 13, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - A Report to the State of Delaware Office of Information Systems on the Subject of Electronic Voting Machines, December 3, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Computerized Voting (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Letter to the Editor of The Washington Post, July 9, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Assuring Accuracy, Integrity and Security in National Elections: The Role of the U.S. Congress, February 12, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Letter to Mr. Buhler, Minority Counsel of Representatives Committee on House Administration, July 11, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Accuracy, Integrity, and Security in Computerized Voting (with Emphasis on Federal Elections), July 1, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Federal Information Processing Standards Are Needed to Assure Accuracy and Integrity of Vote Tallying in National Elections, September 22, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Letter to Chairman Al Swift, Chairman House Committee on Elections, August 18, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Letter to Mr. Gary Bartlett, Executive Secretary Director, June 8, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Issues in National Planning for the Computerization of Elections, December 17, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Letter to the Boston Globe Editor, October 12, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Assessment of Computerized Voting in Brazil with Recommendations for Nations of the Region, October 31, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Adopting Computerized Voting in Developing Countries: Comparisons with the U.S. Experience, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Letter to Jerry W. Calvert, Head of Department of Political Science, Montana State University, August 17, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Letter to Jerry W. Calvert, Head of Department of Political Science, Montana State University, October 26, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Votacion Electronica: Ventajas y Desventajas, January 19-21, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Assessment of Japan's New Direct Recording Electronic Voting System, May 26, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Planning for Computerization of Elections in Ecuador, August 1999 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Letter to Sr. Marcelo Soares, November 2, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Conducting Elections in Maryland: Considerations for the Future, January 4, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - National Elections: They're More Difficut that the Moon Landing, Januray 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - The Importance of Research and Standards in Effective Election Administration, May 22, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Notes for Verbal Presentation, May 22, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - A Recommended Federal Role in Election Administration-- A Personal View, May 29, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - "The Use of Pre-Scored Punch Cards Should be Ended", August 29, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Filling the Institutional Void in Election Administration, September 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Letter to Ms. Penelope Bonsall, Director, Office of Election Administration, September 20, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Will Congress Adopt the Consensus on Election Reform?, November 1, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Federalism and the Crisis in Election Administration, October 27, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Implications for Standards and Implementation in Proposed Federal Election Reform Legislation, January 14, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Standards for Elections: Past, Present and Future, January 31, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 144)
- Series V: Palm Beach Post Clippings
  The hard copy finding aid enclosed in box 13, folder 1 was created by the collectors and reflects their understanding/intention as to the contents of the Palm Beach Post Clippings series. Its accuracy cannot be guaranteed.
  - Palm Beach Post hard copy finding aid, Nov. 2000 - November 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Nov. 2000 - October 2001 (Box 13)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Nov. 2001 - May 2002 (Box 14)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Jun. 2002 - Nov. 2002 (Box 15)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Nov. 11, 2000 - Dec. 14, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Dec. 15, 2000 - Dec. 2001 (Box 17)
  - Palm Beach Post Clippings, Jan. 2002 - Nov. 2002 (Box 18)
- Series VI: Mark Seibel's Notes and Files
  - Seibel's Notes - Invoices, February - March, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Seibel's Notes - Paper/article (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Seibel's Notes - FL Circuit Court, Ridder v. Stafford, Stafford v. Miami Herald, March 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Seibel's Notes - Analysis: Palm Beach Ballot Review, February 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Seibel's Notes - E-mail and Miscellaneous Notes, February 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Seibel's Notes - Letter to Phil Meyer Describing Ballot Review Form, December 21, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Seibel's Notes - Recount Results (Formal and Informal), November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Seibel's Notes - Voting Methods & Procedures (Canvas of Returns) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Seibel's Notes - Wall Charts (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Seibel's Notes - FL Circuit Court Ridder v. Stafford, February 8, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Seibel's Notes - BDO #s, March 2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Seibel's Notes - Ballot Review Spreadsheets (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Election Results - Recounts (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Precinct Maps (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Press Center Articles, January 2001 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Recount Optical Results (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fax of Circuit Court Documents to Fred Franklin, January 2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 2 E-mails From Lesley Clark to Mark Seibel, January 2001 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Xerox of Public Records Handbook (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Manual Recount Gain/Loss Report (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Handwritten Recount Calendar, December 2000 - Janurary 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Property of FL Supreme Court - Gore v. Harris, December 8, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Verification Ballot (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Miami Herald Recount Results (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Circuit Court Documents (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Receipt, February 7, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Recount Results (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Escambia County Fax, December 13, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Map of Florida Counties (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Photo of Canvassars, April 5, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Recount Results - Original Results (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Expenses, January - March 2001 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Series VII: Audio Visual Material
  - Trouble in Paradise, V928 (Box 19)
  - CNN Election 2000, V929 (Box 19)